

Game Producer / Project Manager









Highly adaptive and multi-disciplinary Producer / Project Manager with a technical and design background. Experienced in leading interdisciplinary teams in fast-paced environments. Keen eye for quality and risk assessment. Passionate about elevating teams to excellence by ensuring smooth processes and pipelines.

Experience

Production Intern | gumi Asia Pte Ltd - *Final Fantasy Brave Exvius* Sept 2020 – Feb 2021

- Prepared and maintained monthly and weekly event lists for content updates with <u>Google Sheets</u> and <u>Confluence</u>
- Responsible for Design team's Sprint Planning and follow up with Jira
- Assisted Associate Producer in integrating new ticketing workflow
- Took initiative to streamline and <u>automate</u> various production workflows
- Involved in <u>documentation</u> of notes for marketing promotional videos

Production Teaching Assistant | DigiPen Singapore - *GAM200/250* Sept 2019 – Mar 2020

- Advised student game teams on project scoping and task scheduling
- Mediated cross-discipline discussions and conflicts

Projects

Producer, Editor Programmer, Cinematics Designer

Kindred | Sept 2019 – June 2020, 35 Weeks | 11 Person Team

- 3D single player narrative game developed on a custom C++ engine and editor with C# scripting
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- <u>Communicated</u> game's direction across team members and lecturers
- Adopted <u>Agile</u> methodology with weekly <u>Scrum</u> meetings and <u>Kanban</u> task boards
- Created cross-department workflows for better communication
- Finalist in multiple categories, DigiPen Game Awards 2020

Producer, Engine & Editor Programmer

Mega Macho Brothers | Sept 2018 – Apr 2019, 30 Weeks | 7 Person Team

- 2D co-op action platformer developed on a custom C++ engine and editor
- Led a team with members of various disciplines (Engineering, Design, Art)
- Organized weekly meetings with team members
- Worked with lecturers and team members to resolve internal conflicts
- Awarded Unity Best Sophomore Game, DigiPen Game Awards 2019

For more details on my projects, see my Portfolio!

Education

BSc Computer Science and Game Design

DigiPen Institute of Technology Singapore Sept 2017 – Apr 2021 (Expected)

Dean's Honour List, Fall 2019

Skills

Soft Skills

- Effective Communication
- Problem Solving
- Conflict Resolution
- Task Ownership

Management Methods

- Agile
- Scrum
- Kanban

Management Software

- Jira
- Confluence
- Trello
- Microsoft Excel
- Google Sheets
- HacknPlan

Software & Tools

- Git / SVN
- Microsoft Office
- Visual Studio
- Unity
- Unreal Engine 4
- Custom Game Engine(s)

Programming & Scripting

- C / C++
- C#
- Python
- JavaScript